I don't feel right today
오늘 기분이 안 좋아
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
I always feel like someone is following me
항상 누군가가 나를 따라오는 것 같은 느낌이 든다
Have you tested it?
테스트해보셨나요?
Not found
찾을 수 없음
Are you too sensitive?
너무 예민한가?
It's better to be more sensitive
좀 더 예민해지면 좋을 것 같아요
your relationship with that girl
그 여자와의 관계
How far has it progressed?
어디까지 진행됐나요?
She has already started translating
그녀는 이미 번역을 시작했습니다
The last version of the tender document
입찰 문서의 마지막 버전
You can find an opportunity to start.
시작할 수 있는 기회를 찾을 수 있습니다.
Are things ready?
준비됐나요?
Ready
준비가 된
I'll take her back this weekend
이번 주말에 그녀를 다시 데려갈게요
Will you stay?
당신은 머물 것인가?
you can find a hotel
호텔을 찾을 수 있어요
No need to bring it back
다시 가져올 필요는 없습니다.
I've seen her and her friends
나는 그녀와 그녀의 친구들을 본 적이 있어요
chat record
채팅 기록
She has begun to doubt me
그녀는 나를 의심하기 시작했다
I have another girlfriend
나에겐 다른 여자친구가 있어요
Women's intuition is very accurate
여자의 직감은 매우 정확하다
yes
예
So I have to bring her back
그래서 난 그녀를 다시 데려와야 해
allay her concerns
그녀의 걱정을 덜어주다
Wait until the mission is over
임무가 끝날 때까지 기다리세요
Have to change place again
또 자리를 바꿔야지
Need not
그럴 필요는 없다
I will handle this relationship cleanly
이 관계는 내가 깔끔하게 처리할게
It's you
당신이에요
He must be very busy recently
그 사람 최근에 많이 바빴나 봐요
Never came to the store
한 번도 매장에 온 적이 없어
Don't be impatient with him
그 사람에게 너무 조급해하지 마세요
Not urgent
긴급하지 않음
I won't be in a hurry
난 서두르지 않을 거야
Brought him back
그를 다시 데려왔어
Yao Yao
야오야오
Hello Yaoyao
안녕하세요 야오야오
Something's wrong
문제가 발생했습니다.
Feed uncle
삼촌에게 먹이를 주다
this late
이 늦은 시간
Didn't bother you?
귀찮게 하지 않았나요?
No no
아니 아니
Don't bother, don't bother
귀찮게 하지 마세요, 귀찮게 하지 마세요
you say
당신은 말한다
Is such that
그런가요?
Where are we Zheyue?
우리는 어디에 있습니까?
Opened a new column
새로운 칼럼을 열었습니다
Just invite
그냥 초대하세요
Elites in various fields
다양한 분야의 엘리트
conduct an interview
인터뷰를 하다
would you like to be interviewed
인터뷰를 하고 싶나요?
This matter
이 문제
Yao Yao, I'm sorry
야오야오, 미안해
What about us
어떤 회사 소개
You can't be interviewed casually
함부로 인터뷰하면 안 돼요
Must apply in advance
사전 신청 필수
That's it
그게 다야
Can you please
부탁드려도 될까요
follow us
우리를 따르라
Biological research enthusiasts
생물학 연구에 열광하는 분
Say a few words
몇 마디 말해보세요
We do it in our own name
우리는 우리 자신의 이름으로 그것을 합니다
No professional issues involved
직업적인 문제는 관련되지 않습니다.
If it really doesn’t work, forget it.
정말 효과가 없다면 잊어버리세요.
uncle
삼촌
Zicheng also said
Zicheng도 말했다.
You are usually busy
당신은 평소에 바쁘다
Then go to bed early
그럼 일찍 자러 가세요
Zheyue this website
Zheyue 이 웹사이트
I know
알아요
The content is pretty good
내용은 꽤 괜찮네요
This is me
이게 나야
I will try my best
난 내 최선을 다할 것입니다
I try to take out as much time as possible
나는 최대한 많은 시간을 투자하려고 노력한다.
Can I come to you?
내가 당신에게 갈 수 있나요?
Really
정말
That's great
훌륭해요
Then let's make an appointment tomorrow
그럼 내일 약속하자
How about uncle
삼촌은 어때요?
tomorrow
내일
Then let's
그럼 하자
Take advantage of your lunch break
점심시간을 활용하세요
OK
좋아요
Then I'll see my uncle tomorrow
그럼 내일 삼촌을 만나러 갈게
OK OK
그래 그래
goodbye
안녕히 가세요
good
좋은
Uncle has already agreed
삼촌은 이미 동의했어요
What about tomorrow?
내일은 어때?
I'll try my best to buy you time
나는 당신에게 시간을 벌기 위해 최선을 다할 것입니다
I'll leave the rest to you
나머지는 너에게 맡길게
can you do it
당신은 그것을 할 수 있습니다
Even if it doesn’t work, it has to work.
작동하지 않더라도 작동해야 합니다.
Let's do it now
지금 하자
There is another job
또 다른 직업이 있어요
What job
어떤 직업
Bargaining
교섭
this task
이 작업
Worth at least five thousand gold coins
최소 5천 금화의 가치
right
오른쪽
There must be rewards for doing tasks
일을 하면 보상이 있어야 한다
No more
더 이상은 없어
The bonus is half for each of us
보너스는 우리 각자에게 절반입니다
make a deal
거래를하다
This is still a game
이건 아직 게임이야
If you are in Macau
마카오에 계시다면
That document we got
우리가 받은 그 문서
It's fine if it's fake
가짜라면 괜찮아
It was originally fake
원래는 가짜였어
All this
이 모든 것
It's just a game
이건 그냥 게임 일 뿐이야
Believe me
나를 믿어
Wait until the game is over
게임이 끝날 때까지 기다리세요
We will definitely make it ashore successfully
우리는 반드시 성공적으로 해변에 도착할 것입니다
I trust you
나는 당신을 신뢰합니다
Already reported to group leaders
이미 그룹 리더에게 보고됨
Be extremely careful when performing tasks
작업을 수행할 때 매우 주의하십시오.
Mr. Huang
황 씨
Please help me take a look
좀 도와주세요
this computer
이 컴퓨터
Why can't I connect?
왜 연결할 수 없나요?
OK
좋아요
Hello technical department
안녕하세요 기술부서입니다
Mr. Huang’s office network
Mr. Huang의 사무실 네트워크
Unable to connect
연결할 수 없습니다
Find someone to come and take a look
와서 구경할 사람을 찾아보세요
right away
곧
Come in come in
들어와 들어와
Didn't expect that
그건 예상하지 못했어
So do you
그래서 당신을
need my day
내 하루가 필요해
hurry up hurry up
서둘러 서둘러
Please help me take a look
좀 도와주세요
OK
좋아요
Let me see
좀 보자
Don't mess with me
나한테 장난치지 마
What a mess
정말 엉망이야
I'm going to have guests later.
나중에 손님이 오기로 할게요.
I know
알아요
Isn’t it Yao Yao?
야오야오 아닌가요?
Not an outsider
아웃사이더가 아니다
Be serious about your work attitude
당신의 업무 태도에 대해 진지하게 생각하십시오
Is the leader
리더인가
Miss Yao
미스 야오
Hello
안녕하세요
I'm Mr. Huang's secretary
저는 황 선생님의 비서입니다
Mr. Huang is waiting for you in the office
황 선생님이 사무실에서 당신을 기다리고 계십니다
Let's go straight there
바로 거기로 가자
Hello
안녕하세요
Wait a mininute
잠시만 기다려주세요
explain
설명하다
Mr. Huang
황 씨
Yao Yao from Zheyue Company has arrived
Zheyue Company의 Yao Yao가 도착했습니다.
Then let her come up directly
그럼 그녀가 직접 나타나게 해주세요
She told us about the exhibition area on the first floor
1층 전시장에 대해 알려주셨어요
particularly interested in
특히 관심이 있는
I would like to invite you to visit there
나는 당신을 그곳으로 초대하고 싶습니다.
Well
잘
Then let her
그럼 그녀를 보자
Wait for me in the exhibition area
전시장에서 기다려주세요
I happened to be with her
나는 우연히 그녀와 함께 있었다
Give a good introduction
소개를 잘 해주세요
how's it going
어떻게되고 있습니까
It will take a while
시간이 좀 걸릴 거예요
What about after you fix it?
고치고 나면 어떻습니까?
Turn off the computer for me
나 대신 컴퓨터 좀 꺼줘
close the door
문을 닫다
no problem
괜찮아요
It’s almost time today
오늘 시간이 거의 다 됐어
uncle
삼촌
And one last question
그리고 마지막 질문 하나
Last question
마지막 질문
good
좋은
Mr. Huang
황 씨
The computer has been repaired
컴퓨터가 수리되었습니다
The data is all here
자료는 다 여기에 있어요
Submit this one
이것을 제출하세요
The data has been fine-tuned
데이터가 미세 조정되었습니다.
OK
좋아요
this is for you
이건 널위한거야
Well done
잘하셨어요
When will the bonus be given to me?
보너스는 언제 지급되나요?
After inspection
검사 후
If not, how can you test it?
그렇지 않다면 어떻게 테스트할 수 있나요?
Feeling guilty
죄책감
I have no guilty conscience
나는 죄책감이 없다
I'm just afraid you'll default on your debt
난 단지 당신이 빚을 갚지 못할까봐 두렵습니다.
As long as you complete the task well
임무를 잘 마치기만 하면
I guarantee your income
당신의 수입을 보장해 드립니다
will soon exceed
곧 초과할 것이다
anyone around you
당신 주변의 누구든지
I'm afraid that I have more money than them.
내가 그들보다 돈이 더 많아서 걱정이에요.
Lifespan is shorter than theirs
수명은 그들보다 짧다.
It's up to you
그것은 당신에게 달렸습니다
Don't make arrangements for me recently
최근에 나를 위해 준비하지 마세요
What's the mission?
임무는 무엇입니까?
I want to get familiar with the environment
환경에 익숙해지고 싶다
This will help me extend my life
이것은 내 수명을 연장하는 데 도움이 될 것입니다
Walk
걷다
Are you still worried?
아직도 걱정이 되시나요?
I just took a look
방금 살펴봤는데
Still didn’t pass review
아직 심사를 통과하지 못함
How can it be so fast?
어떻게 그렇게 빠를 수 있나요?
How will they review it?
그들은 그것을 어떻게 검토할 것인가?
I don't know either
나도 모르겠어요
you say
당신은 말한다
will they
그들은 그럴 것인가?
The problem has been discovered
문제가 발견되었습니다
Just stop being so guilty.
너무 죄책감을 갖지 마세요.
I didn’t change it blindly.
맹목적으로 바꾸지 않았습니다.
I am holding the previous data.
이전 데이터를 보유하고 있습니다.
fine-tuning
미세 조정
They can't know
그들은 알 수 없어
unless
~하지 않는 한
Unless something
뭔가가 아니면
you
너
Suspect me
나를 의심해 보세요
You can't
당신은 할 수 없습니다
I swear
맹세해요
I will never betray you
나는 결코 당신을 배신하지 않을 것입니다
Not now
지금은 아님
Not in the future
앞으로는 안 돼
I trust you
나는 당신을 신뢰합니다
You don't have to worry anymore
더 이상 걱정하지 않아도 돼요
As long as we don't say anything
우리가 아무 말도 하지 않는 한
They can't know
그들은 알 수 없어
Don't worry
괜찮아요
Waiting for you to finish eating in a while
잠시 후에 식사가 끝날 때까지 기다리세요.
Let's shift our attention
관심을 돌리자
take you to a place
당신을 어떤 곳으로 데려가세요
vent your anxiety
불안을 해소하라
where to
어디로
Did you catch it?
잡았나요?
This one, this one
이거, 이거
Crooked
구부러진
Almost almost
거의 거의
Come up, come up
올라와, 올라와
Ok, Ok
그래 그래
good
좋은
Another one comes out
또 하나 나오네요
gave it to you
당신에게 줬어요
Thanks
감사해요
come on! Come on
어서! 어서
come on
어서 해봐요
A little closer
좀 더 가까이
You are so stupid
당신은 정말 바보입니다
This is okay, okay
이건 괜찮아, 알았어
This is good
이것은 좋다
I caught this
나는 이것을 잡았다
come on! Come on
어서! 어서
come on, come on, come on
어서, 어서, 어서
five little dolls
다섯 개의 작은 인형
Get a bigger doll
더 큰 인형을 사세요
Which one is more cost-effective?
어느 것이 더 비용 효율적인가요?
It’s definitely a good deal for a big baby
확실히 큰 아기한테는 좋은 일이겠죠
How about it
어때요?
I feel better now, right?
이제 기분이 나아졌죠?
Much more comfortable
훨씬 더 편안해요
And today
그리고 오늘
I caught more than you
내가 너보다 더 많이 잡았어
I caught these
나는 이것들을 잡았다
It sounds like
처럼 들린다
When did I win over you?
내가 언제 당신을 이겼나요?
I appreciate you like this
이렇게 고맙게 생각해요
Ambitious
거창한
surrender type
항복 유형
What shall we play later?
나중에 뭐하고 놀까?
Wait a minute
잠깐 기다려요
Go to the skating rink
스케이트장으로 가세요
OK
좋아요
Then I've booked a ticket
그럼 표를 예매했어요
You weren't asleep at all, were you?
당신은 전혀 잠들지 않았죠?
I thought you were really not anxious
정말 불안하지 않을 줄 알았는데
I didn’t expect that we are evenly matched.
나는 우리가 균등하게 일치할 것이라고 기대하지 않았습니다.
What's going on between us?
우리 사이에 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
There has to be someone
누군가가 있어야 해
keep calm
침착하게 지내다
Otherwise everything will collapse
그렇지 않으면 모든 것이 무너질 것이다
I really don't like this feeling
난 이 느낌이 정말 싫어
Might as well give it to me
나한테 주는 게 나을지도 몰라
Let's have a good time
즐거운 시간을 보내자
Forget it
잊어 버려
Everything has been done
모든 것이 완료되었습니다.
Just leave it to fate
그냥 운명에 맡기세요
What if
만약
There really will be a day
정말 그런 날이 있겠지
Photos on Dr. Feng’s computer
Feng 박사의 컴퓨터에 있는 사진
I stole it
내가 훔쳤어
I also stole the documents in Macau.
마카오에서도 문서를 훔쳤어요.
There are also those in Lao Huang’s computer
Lao Huang의 컴퓨터에도 그런 것이 있습니다
that report
그 보고서
I stole it all
내가 다 훔쳤어
I'm in the middle
나는 중간에있다
What tricks did you do?
무슨 트릭을 썼나요?
you have no idea
당신은 전혀 모른다
Spy asks you
스파이가 당신에게 묻습니다.
Just say that
그냥 그렇게 말해
Remember?
기억하다?
I'm worried about you
나는 당신에 대해 걱정
Do not worry
걱정 하지마
I have a big heart
나는 마음이 크다
Fate is also great
운명도 위대하다
fine
괜찮은
Go to sleep
자러 가세요
Documents handed over by Huang Zicheng
황자성이 건네준 서류
has a problem
문제가 있다
some data
일부 데이터
Changed it for him
그 사람을 위해 바꿨어요
Sure enough, he has a problem
물론 그 사람도 문제가 있는 거겠죠
I originally thought
나는 원래 생각했다
Put him in the network department
그를 네트워크 부서에 넣어라
no need
필요 없음
we have people there
거기 사람들이 있어
Putting one more is redundant
하나 더 넣는 건 무리
Now it seems
이제는 것 같다
you are right
당신 말이 맞아요
Originally, Huang Zicheng
원래는 황자성
Put it in the network department
네트워크 부서에 넣어
To find a scapegoat for him
그를 위한 희생양을 찾기 위해
Just like Shi Lei and Yu Xiaoyue
Shi Lei와 Yu Xiaoyue처럼
Once there is a problem
일단 문제가 생기면
Throw the chess piece
체스 말을 던져
Keep Huang Zicheng
황자성(Huang Zicheng)을 지켜라
But after I met him in the bar
하지만 바에서 그를 만난 후
I think it's not that simple
내 생각엔 그게 그렇게 간단하지 않은 것 같아
so
그래서
I give him a task
나는 그에게 임무를 준다
Come and test the truth
와서 진실을 시험해 보세요
What do you think of Huang Zicheng?
황자성에 대해 어떻게 생각하시나요?
Doing such a small act without permission
이런 작은 행동을 허락도 없이 하다니
It's his personal behavior
그 사람의 개인적인 행동이에요
Or is there someone behind him?
아니면 뒤에 누군가가 있는 걸까요?
Contact Fang Lu
팡루에게 연락하기
Change data
데이터 변경
these behaviors
이러한 행동
It seems that the purpose is not simple.
목적은 간단하지 않은 것 같습니다.
Then you doubt
그럼 당신은 의심
Instigated behind his back
등 뒤에서 선동됨
It's the National Security Agency
국가안보국이다
It's possible
있을 수있다
What about Yao Yao?
야오야오는 어떻습니까?
Did Yao Yao remind him?
Yao Yao가 그에게 상기시켰나요?
No
아니요
I suggest starting with Yao Yao
야오야오(Yao Yao)부터 시작하는 것이 좋습니다.
See how much she knows
그녀가 얼마나 알고 있는지 확인해보세요
Huang Zicheng now
지금 황쯔쳉
Already a dangerous person
이미 위험한 사람
Is the national security hidden behind him?
그 뒤에 국가 안보가 숨겨져 있습니까?
Still unknown
아직 알려지지 않음
Before I figure it out
내가 알아내기 전에
Don't touch him first
그 사람을 먼저 만지지 마세요.
I will take care of Yao Yao's side.
야오야오 옆은 내가 챙길게.
OK
좋아요
Just specialized
그냥 전문적으로
is this your car
이것은 너의 차냐
this is mine
이 내 꺼야
this is yours
이것은 당신 것입니다
Whose does this belong to?
이것은 누구의 것입니까?
This is mine
이 내 꺼야
can i try
내가 해봐도 돼
sure
확신하는
let me try your car
네 차를 시험해 볼게
Are these two cars the same?
이 두 차는 같은 차인가요?
These two cars are different
이 두 차는 서로 다릅니다
Displacement is different
변위가 다릅니다
What about that one?
그거 어때요?
It's similar to that one
그거랑 비슷해요
Then these two are almost the same.
그렇다면 이 둘은 거의 같습니다.
right
오른쪽
But it was actually modified
그런데 실제로 수정됐네요
a little more than that
그보다 조금 더
Your car is so handsome
당신 차는 너무 멋져요
Thanks
감사해요
Not bad, really handsome
나쁘지 않아, 정말 잘생겼어
OK
좋아요
So let’s get here today
그럼 오늘은 여기까지 하자
Then I'll go back first
그럼 나 먼저 돌아갈게
Let's play again in two days
이틀 뒤에 다시 놀자
OK
좋아요
Date again
다시 데이트
Bye bye
안녕
he's gone
그는 갔어요
Hi-tech
하이테크
Pony follows up
포니가 후속 조치를 취함
Technical subjects start
기술 과목 시작
Already started
이미 시작됨
Everyone remember
다들 기억해
keep Calm
침착함을 유지하다
Better to lose than to be violent
폭력을 행사하는 것보다 잃는 것이 낫습니다
I'm in place
나는 제자리에있다
Take Kehua Middle Road
Kehua Middle Road 이용
parallel to him
그와 평행
He entered Huainan North Road
그는 회남북로에 진입했다
The target is at Huainan North Road
목표는 Huainan North Road에 있습니다.
Big Liu
빅 리우
Follow him at the next intersection
다음 교차로에서 그를 따라가세요
receive
받다
He stopped the car
그는 차를 멈췄다
Entered a flower shop
꽃집에 들어갔다
Don't stop and pass by
멈추지 말고 지나쳐라
hello sir
안녕하세요 선생님
what flowers do you want
무슨 꽃을 원해요?
Give me a bouquet of roses
나에게 장미 꽃다발을 줘
Wait a moment
잠깐만요
He should arrive at his destination soon
그는 곧 목적지에 도착할 것이다
The suspect is at the gate of the high-speed rail group
용의자는 고속철도 집단의 게이트에 있다
stopped
중지됨
Liu took over
Liu가 인수했습니다.
continue to follow
계속 따라가다
Did you see the girl's face clearly?
소녀의 얼굴을 똑똑히 보셨나요?
Can't see the face
얼굴이 안보여
You first go to the 10th floor, Building 11, Area B
먼저 B구역 11동 10층으로 가세요.
Set the password to your birthday
생일에 맞춰 비밀번호를 설정하세요
You go up first
너 먼저 올라가
I'm going to park the car
차를 주차할 거예요
I'll follow up and have a look
팔로우하고 살펴볼게요
Stop following
팔로우 중지
The girl is unidentified
그 소녀는 신원이 불명이다
It's too risky to follow.
따라가는 것은 너무 위험합니다.
Wait for her to come out
그녀가 나올 때까지 기다리세요
good
좋은
Hello, please come in
안녕하세요, 들어오세요
Just ignore it
그냥 무시하세요
Won't it burn?
안 타나요?
We just want its skin
우리는 단지 그 피부를 원할 뿐이에요
That layer of burnt
그 탄탄한 층
That's called Mena's reaction
메나의 반응이라고 하네요
I didn’t expect you to be so good at cooking
네가 이렇게 요리를 잘할 줄은 몰랐어
I studied cooking in high school
고등학교 때 요리를 공부했어요
Really
정말
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
How many other things can you do?
당신은 얼마나 많은 다른 일을 할 수 있나요?
I do not know
모르겠어요
a lot of
많은
Do you really not care about it?
정말 신경 안 쓰시나요?
It's time to turn over
뒤집을 시간이야
thanks for your dinnere
저녁 식사 감사합니다
delicious
맛있는
The red wine you chose is also great
당신이 선택한 레드와인도 맛있어요
It's for you
그것은 당신을 위해
Why are there gifts?
선물은 왜 있는 걸까요?
Today is an important day
오늘은 중요한 날이에요
today
오늘
do not you know
몰랐 니
Today is
오늘은
buckley galaxy
버클리 갤럭시
1,350th anniversary of the explosion
폭발 1,350주년
anniversary
기념일
Come as soon as you open your mouth
입 열자마자 와
unimportant
중요하지 않은
See if you like it
마음에 드는지 확인해보세요
Also round
또한 둥근
my name
내 이름
try
노력하다
How about it
어때요?
Got promoted
승진했어요
Senior Assistant
수석 비서
Isn't that still an assistant?
아직도 조수 아닌가요?
But high-end
하지만 고급형
We have to drink to this
우리는 이것까지 마셔야 해
wish
소망
Happy promotion
즐거운 프로모션
buckley galaxy
버클리 갤럭시
1,350th anniversary of the explosion
폭발 1,350주년
Can
할 수 있다
Let me give you a gift too
나도 선물하자
I also have a gift
나도 선물이 있어
come over
이리와
receive
받다
You cook and I wash the dishes
너는 요리하고 나는 설거지를 한다
Reasonable
합리적인
Let's go together
같이 가자
The sun is at the gate of the community
태양은 공동체의 문에 있다
The suspect has not been seen again.
용의자는 다시 나타나지 않았습니다.
The girl never came out again
그 여자는 다시는 나오지 않았어
Have you confirmed the girl's identity?
그 소녀의 신원을 확인하셨나요?
I didn't see the girl's face clearly
나는 그 여자의 얼굴을 똑똑히 보지 못했다.
So there is nothing I can do to her
그러니까 내가 그 사람한테 할 수 있는 게 아무것도 없어.
for identification
식별을 위해
But that girl
그런데 그 여자
When I left the high-speed rail group
고속철도그룹을 탈퇴했을 때
Carrying a bag
가방을 들고
probably there
아마 거기 있을 거야
employees
직원
Fang Yongping explained
Fang Yongping이 설명했습니다.
Ye Wu is watching
이우가 보고 있다
High-speed rail group’s bid
고속철도그룹 입찰
So their actions
그래서 그들의 행동은
It's probably still going on
아마 아직도 계속되고 있을 거야
Do it to them both
둘 다한테 해라
24-hour monitoring
24시간 모니터링
Three groups take turns monitoring
3개 그룹이 교대로 모니터링
Be sure to make it clear
꼭 밝혀두세요
The identity of this girl
이 소녀의 정체
clear
분명한
If this girl
이 여자라면
work there
거기서 일하다
It will definitely appear tomorrow
내일은 꼭 나타날 거야
She likes the gift you gave her
그 사람은 당신이 준 선물을 좋아해요
I really like it
난 정말 좋아
Still pretending to like it
아직도 좋아하는 척
unimportant
중요하지 않은
The most important thing is to successfully complete the task
가장 중요한 것은 작업을 성공적으로 완료하는 것입니다.
Do not worry
걱정 하지마
Time flies so fast
세월 참 빠르다
This is our partnership
이것이 우리의 파트너십이다
What year is it?
몇 년입니까?
more than three years
3년 이상
Boss Zhang
장보스
from now on
지금부터
I am your wife
나는 당신의 아내입니다
How long
얼마나 오래
Listen to the organization's arrangements
조직의 준비사항을 듣습니다.
Can
할 수 있다
Couple I haven’t seen for a long time
오랜만에 보는 커플
Should I be more enthusiastic?
좀 더 열심이라고 해야 하나?
Let's take you home
당신을 집으로 데려가자
Gift
선물
Very considerate
매우 사려 깊음
Sorry, I am late
미안해요, 늦었어요
It doesn't matter
그것은 중요하지 않습니다
Sir, your wine
선생님, 와인
Thanks
감사해요
thanks, thanks
감사 감사
Very good
매우 좋은
cheers
건배
Nothing good will happen to you when you come here
여기 오면 아무 좋은 일도 일어나지 않을 거야
Good news for you
당신에게 좋은 소식
Your task here
여기서 당신의 임무
It has ended
끝났어
what's next
무엇 향후 계획
You guys will go to one
너희들은 한 번 가볼게
very beautiful place
매우 아름다운 곳
China Tsukai
중국 쓰카이
long-term latent
장기 잠재
Taking over on behalf of the organization
조직을 대신하여 인수
Jinhai affairs
진해사무
So are we still husband and wife?
그럼 우리는 여전히 남편과 아내인가요?
No
아니요
You will have your own tasks
당신은 당신 자신의 임무를 갖게 될 것입니다
Divorced
이혼
Single
하나의
Happy three years
3년 잘 보내세요